

Bogor

**** 0896-1427-6492

□ anggaprytna@gmail.com

anggaprytn.com

in linkedin.com/in/anggaprytn

Summary

Highly passionate about Application Development and UI/UX Design. Experienced in developing mobile applications using frameworks React Native, Redux, Node.JS, Express.JS with REST API and knowledge in databases, such as MySQL, PostgreSQL, and MongoDB. And also experienced in Graphic Design being able using Adobe Photoshop, CorelDRAW, and Adobe Illustrator.

Skills

Programming Languages

PHP, JavaScript, HTML, CSS/Sass, and TypeScript.

Frameworks

React Native, Express.JS, Node.JS, Redux, and Wordpress

Database

PostgreSQL, MongoDB, and MySQLi.

Graphic Design

Adobe Photoshop, CorelDRAW, Adobe Illustrator, and Adobe Lightroom.

Work experience

Front-End Mobile Developer

Sep 2019 - Present

Klola Indonesia

Responsibilities:

- Build, Design and Improve the Android/iOS Mobile App.
- Developing Mobile Application for Android/iOS.

Talent (Full Stack Developer)

Aug 2019 - Present

Arkademy

- · Learning about React Native, Node.JS, Express.JS, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, Redux, & REST API.
- Developing Mobile Application for Android/iOS.

Freelance Graphic Designer

Des 2016 - Sep 2017

Sang Vectoria Jenaka

Converting images into cartoon vectors using Photoshop, CorelDRAW, and Adobe Illustrator.

Achievement

1st Winner - Website & Blog WordPress Competition

Feb - 2017

Mercu Buana University Campus D

Designing Website & Blog WordPress about Mercu Buana University Campus D.

Education

SMK Yadika 11 Jatirangga

2014 - 2017

Computer and Network Engineering Learning about Computer Systems and Networking.